Constitution Collection 6035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Chain Makers National Union of USA, 1903 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Chemical Workers, International Union of, 1944-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Christian Labor Association, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Cigar Makers' International Union of America, 1885-1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Civil Service Employees Association, 1966-2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- CSEA State, County & Municipal Employees, American Federation of, 1981-1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Cleaning & Dyehouse Workers, International Assoc., 1938-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Cloak, Suit & Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., 1946 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Clothing Cutters & Trimmers, Brotherhood (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Clothing & Textile Workers Union, Amalgamated, 1976-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Clothing Workers of America, Amalgamated, 1915-1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1977-2008 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Communication Association, American, 1938-1956 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Communications Workers of America, 1950-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers of America, 1950-2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Community and Social Agency Employees Union (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Conductors, Order of Sleeping Car, 1918-1947 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Confederated Unions of America, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Coopers International Union of North America, 1919-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Correction Officers Benevolent Assoc., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Department Store Workers of America, United, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Diamond Workers Protective Union of America, 1903 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Die Casting Workers National Assoc. of, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Die Sinkers Conference, International, 1946-1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Diesel Workers Union (Ind.), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Directors Guild of America, 1959-1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Distillery, Rectifying & Wine Workers, 1943-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Distillery, Wine & Allied Workers International Union, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Distribution, Processing & Office Workers, 1950-1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  1950, 1965
- Distributive Workers of America, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Distributive Workers Union, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Doll and Toy Workers, 1953-1958 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Education Assoc., National, 1977-1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Educators, New York, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, International Union of IUE, 1955-1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1940-2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, United, 1931-1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers United UE, 1912-2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Electrical Workers Benefit Assoc., 1937-1956 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers, International Union of, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Elevator Constructors, International Union of, 1902-1934 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Elevator Constructors, Operators and Starters, International Union of, 1934-1939 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Elevator Constructors, International Union of, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Engineering Assoc, Southern California Prof., 1952-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Engineering Employees Assoc., Seattle Prof., 1963-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Engineering Personnel, Assoc. of Prof., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Society of Engineers, 1892-1913 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  1892, 1913
- Engineers, American Federation of Technical, 1952-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Engineers and Architects Assoc., 1954-1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Engineers and Scientists of America, 1952-1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Engineers and Scientists of California, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Engineers, Draftsmen & Associates, National Council of, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Engineers International Union of Steam & Operating, 1920-1926 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Engineers, National Assoc. of Stationary, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Engineers of New York, Eccentric Assoc., 1885 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Engravers, Sketchmakers, 1933-1951 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Farm Equipment & Metal Workers of America, United, 1942-1949 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Farm Labor Union, National, 1946-1950 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Farm Workers of America, United, 1973-1984 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Farmers Education & Cooperative Union of America, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Financial Union, Order of the, 1887 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Federal Employees, National Federation of, 1946-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Federal Labor Union, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Federal Workers of America, United, 1942-1944 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Fire Fighters, International Assoc. of, 1923-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Firemen and Oilers, 1898-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Fishermen & Allied Workers of America, International, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Flight Attendants, 1976-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Flight Engineers, International Assoc., 1948-1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Food and Commercial Workers International Union, United, 1979-2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Food Industries International Workers in the Amalgamated, 1920-1923 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Food, Tobacco, Agricultural & Allied Workers Union of America, 1944-1947 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Food Workers, Amalgamated, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Football League Players Assoc., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Foreman's Assoc. of America, 1941-1951 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Foundry of Employees, International Brotherhood of, 1906-1927 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Fur and Leather Workers' Union, International, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Fur Workers Union of U.S. & Canada International, 1912-1939 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- International Fur Workers' Union, Local No. 2, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Furniture Workers of America, United, 1939-1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Garment Workers of America, United, 1918-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Garment Workers Union, International Ladies', 1965-1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers United-CIO, 1942-1952 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers United-CIO, Locals, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  1952, 1953
- Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1954-1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Assoc., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Assoc. of U.S. and Canada, 1913-1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Glass Ceramic & Silica Sand Workers, Federation of, 1940-1950 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Glass Cutters & Flatteners Professional Assoc., Window, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Glass Cutters League of America, Window, 1935-1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics & Allied Workers International Union, 1988-2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Glass, Pottery, Plastics & Allied Workers, 1981-1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Glass Workers of America, Federation of Flat, 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Glass Workers, National Window, 1914-1923 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Glass Workers Union of North America, American Flint (Toledo, OH), 1921-2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Glove Cutters and Shavers, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Glove Workers Union of America, International, 1916-1959 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Government and Civic Employees Org. Com.-, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Government Employees, American Federation of, 1952-1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Government Employees, National Assoc. of, 1971-1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Government Employees, National Assoc. of Aviation Science & Tech Assn., Federal, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Government Employees, National Assoc. of Correctional Officers, International Brotherhood, 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Government Employees, National Assoc. of Municipal Employees, 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Government Employees, National Assoc. of Police, International Brotherhood of, 1971-1980 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Grain Millers, American Federation of, 1948-1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Grain Processors, American Federation of, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Granite Cutters International Assoc. of America, 1909-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Graphic Arts International Union, 1972-1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Graphic Communications International Union, 1983-2001 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Guards Union of America, International, 1953-1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  1953, 1971
- Plant Guard Workers of America, United, 1951-1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Handbag, Luggage, Belt & Novelty Workers, 1942-1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Hat, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union, Cloth, 1913-1927 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Hatters of North America, United, 1898-1920 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Hatters of North America, United, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Hatters, Cap & Millinary Workers International Union, 1934-1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Hod Carriers, BIG. & Common Laborers U. International, 1935-1961 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Hosiery Workers, American Federation of, 1937-1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Hospital and Health Care Employees, National Union of, 1979-1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1957-1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International, AFL, Local, 1947-1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Independent Union Council, National, 1952-1959 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Independent Unions, National Federation of, 1969-1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Independent Workers of North America, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Industrial Trades Unions of America, 1940-1951 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Industrial Workers Assoc., Independent (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Industrial Workers of America, Allied International, 1957-1989 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Industrial Workers, National, 1961-1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Industrial Workers of the World, 1951-1957 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Insurance Agents International Union, 1928-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Insurance Agents, International Union of Life, 1958-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Insurance Workers International Union, 1961-1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Insurance Workers of America, 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Internal Revenue Employees, National Assoc., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- International Assoc. of Bridge Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- International Assoc. of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- International Labor Communications Assoc., 1984-2009 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- International Labor Press Assoc., 1966-1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Iron, Steel & Tin Workers of North America, Amalgamated Assoc. of, 1907-1942 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Iron Workers, International Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental, 1952-1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Jewelry Workers Union, International, 1942-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Knights of Labor, 1888-1911 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Labor Publishing Company, 1910 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, 1961-1995 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Laborers' International Union, Mail Handlers Union, National Postal, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Laborers: Mail Handlers, 1972-1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Lace Operatives of America, Amalgamated, 1909-1937 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  1909, 1937
- Lathers International Union, Wood, Wire & Metal, 1909-1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Laundry and Dry Cleaning International Union, 1960-1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Laundry, Dry Cleaning & Dye House Workers, 1960-1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Laundry Workers' International Workers, 1909-1949 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Leather Goods, Plastics & Novelty Workers Union, 1954-1963 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Leather Workers International Union of America, 1962-1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Leather Workers International Union, United, 1920-1959 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Leather Workers on Horse Goods, International Brotherhood of, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Leather Workers on Horse Goods, United Brotherhood of, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Leather Workers Union of America, Amalgamated, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Letter Carriers of U.S.A., National Assoc., 1931-2006 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Letter Carriers Assoc., the National Rural, 1949-1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Lithographers and Photo Engravers International Union, 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Lithographers of America, Amalgamated, 1930-1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Lithographic Workmen, International Union, 1907 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Locomotive Engineers, International Brotherhood of, 1912-2007 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Locomotive Engineers Mutual Life, 1986-1942 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Locomotive Firemen and Engineers, Brotherhood of, 1881 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Locomotive Firemen and Engineers, Brotherhood of, 1875-1953 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Loggers & Lumbermen, Loay Legion of, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Longshoremen, International Brotherhood of, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Longshoremen, Making & Transport Workers Assoc., International, 1903 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemens' International, 1955-2000 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemens' Union, International, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Longshoremen's Assoc., International, 1919-1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers, International, 1905-1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Machinists, International Assoc. of, 1930-1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Mailers Union, International, 1947-1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Maintenance & Service Emp. Union of North America, Ind., 1947 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of, 1919-1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Marble Cutters & Setters of America, National Assoc. of, 1892 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Marble, Slate & Stone Polishers, Rubbers & Sawers, Tiler & Marble Setters Helpers & Marble Mosaic & Terrazzo Workers Helpers of the U.S. & Canada, International Assoc. of, 1930-1967 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Ind. Union, 1942-1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Marine Engineers, Brotherhood of, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Assoc., National, 1950-1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Marine Officers Assoc., United, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Maritime Union of America, National, 1937-1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Masters, Mates & Pilots of American International Organization, 1953-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Masters, Mates & Pilots National Organization, 1926-1959 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated, 1914-1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Mechanics & Foremen of Navy Yards & Navy Stations, National Assoc. of Master, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Mechanics Educational Society of America, 1950-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Mechanics Independent Union, United Maintenance, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Messengers, National Assoc. of Special Delivery, 1939-1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Metal & Enamelware Workers International Council of Fabricated, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Metal Engravers Union International, 1942-1950 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Metal Mechanics, International Assoc. of Allied, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Metal Polishers' International Union, 1919-1924 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers, and Helpers International Union, 1903-1959 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Metal Workers Brotherhood of, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers International, 1918-1965 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Mine Workers of America, Progressive, 1940-2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Mine Workers of America, United, 1908-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Mine Workers of America, United District 50, 1944-1968 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Miners of America, Progressive, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- United Mine Workers, United Construction Workers, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Molders and Allied Workers Union, International, 1966-1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Molders and Foundry Workers Union of North America, International, 1940-1960 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Molders Union of North America, International, 1928-1956 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Molders Union of North America, Iron, 1890-1902 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  1890, 1902
- Mulespinners Assoc. of America, National Cotton, 1890 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Musicians, American Federation of, 1907-1952 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Musicians, American Federation of, 1907-1952 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Musicians, American Federation of, 1907-1952 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Musicians, American Federation of, 1907-1952 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- National Independent Union Council, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- National Joint Industrial Council for the Surgical Dressing Industry, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- National Unemployment Council of the U.S.A., 1934 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Needletrades, Industrial & Textile Employees, Union of, 1995-1999 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Negro American Labor Council, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union, 1959-1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Guild, The, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Guild, American, 1940-1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Guild, American, 1940-1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Nurses Assoc., American, 1974-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Office Employees International Union, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Office and Professional Workers of America, United, 1938-1948 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Office and Professional Employees, International Union, 1969-1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Office Employees International Union, Local, 1903-1949 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Office, Sales, Technical Employees Assoc., 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers International Councils and, 1950-1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Oil Field, Gas Well & Refinery Workers International Assoc., 1920-1934 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Oil Workers International Union (CIO), 1937-1954 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Operating Engineers, International Union of, 1938-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Optical and Instrument Workers of America, United, 1949-1950 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Oregon Public Employees Union, 1982-1988 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Packinghouse and Dairy Workers, National Brotherhood, 1962-1963 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Packinghouse, Food & Allied Workers United, 1960-1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Packinghouse Workers, National Brotherhood, 1944-1958 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Painters and Allied Trades, International Brotherhood of, 1975-2010 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Painters and Allied Trades, International Brotherhood of, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, 1913-1955 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers of America, Brotherhood of, Locals, 1908-1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical & Energy Workers International Union, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Paper, Novelty & Toy Workers International Union, Unit., 1940-1943 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Papermakers, International Brotherhood of, 1918-1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Papermakers and Paperworkers, United, 1940-1967 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Paperworkers International Union, United, 1972-1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Paperworkers of America, United, 1947-1953 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Paperworkers Organizing Committee, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Patrolmen's Benevolent Assoc. of the City of New York, 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  1959, 1971
- Pattern Makers' League, 1909-1982 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Paving Cutters' Union International, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Paving Cutters' Union of the United States of America and Canada, 1909-1948 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Personnel in Employment Security, International Assoc. of, 1982-1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Petroleum Workers, Independent Union of, 1950-1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Photo Engravers' Union of North America, International, 1950-1983 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Piano, Organ & Musical Instrument Workers' International Union of America, 1902-1911 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Piano and Organ Makers of America, Professional & Ben. Union, 1883 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Piano Workers, Independent Union of (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Pilots Assoc., Allied, 1972-1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Plasterers' and Cement Finishers International Assoc., Operative, 1907-1941 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Plasterers and Cement Masons International Assoc., Operative, 1941-1994 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Plasterers' International Assoc., Operative, 1908 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Plate Printers, Dye Stampers, 1947-1963 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Plate Printers, International Steel and Copper Union, North America, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Plaything, Jewelry & Novelty Workers International Union, 1944-1950 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Plumbers & Steam Fitters, United Assoc. of, 1902-1938 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Plumbing & Pipefitting Ind. Of the U.S. & Canada, United Assoc. of Journeymen & Apprentices, 1919- 1991 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Pocketbook Workers Union, International, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Police Benevolent Assoc. Local, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Police Conference, State Local, 1899-1959 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  1899, 1959
- Post Office & General Services Maintenance Employees, National Assoc. of, 1952-1966 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Post Office & Postal Trans. Service, Mail Handlers, Watchmen and Mess. National Assoc., 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Post Office and Railway Mail Handlers, National Assoc., 1952 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Post Office Clerks, National Federation of, 1915-1958 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Post Office Clerks of the United States, United National Assoc. of, 1903-1935 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  1903, 1935
- Post Office Craftsmen, United National, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Post Office Motor Vehicle Employees, 1946-1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Postal and Federal Employees, National Alliance of, 1970-1990 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Postal Clerks, United Federation of, 1959-1966 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Postal Employees, National Alliance, 1947-1961 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  1947, 1961
- Postal Supervisors, National Assoc. of, 1947-1960 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Postal Transport Assoc., National, 1948-2004 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Postal Union, National, 1962-1966 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Postal Workers Union, American, 1982-2006 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Postmasters, District, National League of, 1940-1953 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Postmasters, National Assoc. of, 1971-1975 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Postmasters of the U.S., National League of, 1955-1988 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Post Office and General Service Maintenance Employees, National Assoc. of, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers & Group Leaders, National Assoc., 1963-1965 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Potters, National Brotherhood of Operative, 1902-1965 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Pottery and Allied Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1970-1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Powder and High Explosive Workers of America, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Printers Beneficial Assoc. of the U.S., Machine, 1882 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Printing and Graphic Communications Union, 1972-1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Printing Pressmen & Assists. Union of North America, International, 1912-1966 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Printing Trades Council, Allied, 1919-1953 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Probation Officers Assoc. & Retirement Welfare Funds, United (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Professional and Technical Engineers, International Federation of, 1975-1981 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Public Employees Federation, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Public Workers of America, United, 1946-1950 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Pulp and Paper Workers, Western, 1965-1989 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Pulp, Sulphite & Papermill Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1935-1971 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Pulp, Sulphite & Papermill Workers, International Brotherhood of, Local, 1947-1960 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Quarry Workers, 1906-1930 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Radio and Television Directors Guild, 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 2)